Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. Typed L.s.(John Foord) to [William] [Woodville] [Rockhill]; [n.p., n.d.], (815); 1l.
    The firstr part of this letter is wanting.
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 19 May 1904., (816); 1l.
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. Typed L.s.(John Foord) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 24 Jun 1904., (817); 2l.
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. Typed L.s.(John Foord) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 4 Oct 1904., (818); 4l.
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 9 Sep [1913]., (819); ([2]p.)
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 12 Sep [1913]., (820); ([1]p.)
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Kerhonkson, 16 Sep [1913]., (821); ([3]p.)
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Kerhonkson, 18 Sep [1913]., (822); ([2]p.)
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. Typed L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 1 Oct 1913., (823); 1l.
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 3 Oct [1913]., (824); ([2]p.)
  - Foord, John, 1842-1922. A.L.s.(John Foord) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 6 Jun [1914]., (825); ([2]p.)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. A.L.s.(John W. Foster) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 2 Sep [189-?], (826); 1l.
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. A.L.s.(John W. Foster) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 27 Aug 1896., (827); ([1]p.)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. Ms.L.s.(John W.Foster) to James H. Wilson; Washington, 22 Sep 1892., (827a); ([3]p.)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. A.L.s.(John W. Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Henderson Harbor, 22 Jul 1900., (828); ([2]p.)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. A.L.s.(John W. Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Henderson Harbor, 27 Jul 1900., (829); ([3]p.)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917. A.L.s.(John W. Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 19 Oct 1900., (830); 1l.
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [London] 10 Jan [1895]., (831); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville Rockhill?]; London, 13 Nov [1897]., (831a); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 16 Dec [1897]., (831b); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 5 Jan 1898., (832); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 5 Feb [1898]., (833); ([3]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 29 Mar [1898]., (834); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 13 Apr [1898]., (835); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 25 May [1898]., (836); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 24 Jun [1898]., (837); ([3]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 5 Aug [1898]., (838); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 5 Dec [1898]., (839); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 15 Dec [1898]., (840); ([3]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 27 Jan [1899]., (841); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 12 Feb [1899]., (842); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Westminster, 17 Mar [1899]., (843); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 19 Apr [1899]., (844); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wanstead, 3 Jun [1899]., (845); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 28 Jun [1899]., (846); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 21 Jul [1899]., (847); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 27 Sep [1899]., (848); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- Typed L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 11 Nov 1899., (849); 2l.
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 24 Nov [1899]., (850); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Forest Gate, [190-?], (851); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- Typed L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 1 Jan 1900., (852); [2]p.
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 2 Feb 1900., (853); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 21 Feb 1900., (854); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 27 Feb 1900., (855); [2]p.
  - Foster, William, 1863- Typed L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 19 Mar 1900., (856); [2]p.
  - Foster, William, 1863- Typed L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 24 Apr 1900. [2]l., (857)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 5 May 1900. n, (858); ([4]p.)
  - Foster, William, 1863- A.L.s.(William Foster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 22 May 1900., (859); ([2]p.)
  - Foulk, Clayton, M. A.L.s.(Clayton M. Foulk) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Brooklyn, 21 Oct 1894., (860); ([4]p.)
  - Foulk, Clayton M. A.L.s.(Clayton M. Foulk) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Brooklyn, 9 Dec 1894., (861); ([3]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C. Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Pepying, 23 De [1896]., (862); [2]p.
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893, A.L.s.(Geo.C.F.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 25 Jan [1887]., (862a); ([8]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(G.C.F.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 25 Jan [1887]., (862b); ([4]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Nagasaki 4 Feb [1887]., (862c); ([8]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Nagasaki 6 Feb [1887]., (862d); ([4]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C. Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Nagasaki, 28 Fe [1887]., (863); ([16]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C. Foulk) to "Dear Iwa-yamma sam"; Soul, 2 Apr [1887]., (864); ([2]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.(part with signature wanting) to [William Woodville] Rockhill Soul, 29 Apr [1887]., (864a); ([4]p.)
    The latter part of this letter is wanting.
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C. Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Soul, 7 May [1887]., (864b); ([16]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C. Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Soul, 12 May [1887]., (864c); ([7]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Soul, 26 May [1887]., (864d); ([12]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Soul. 14 Jun [1887]., (864e); ([13]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Kobe, 3 Sep [1887]., (864f); ([8]p.)
  - Foulk, George Clayton, 1856-1893. A.L.s.(George C.Foulk) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tokyo, 13 Jul [1888]., (864g); ([8]p.)
  - Foucaux, P Y A.L.s.(P.Y.Foucaux) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 11[?] Apr 1883., (864h); ([3]p.)
  - Foucaux, P Y A.L.s.(P.Y.Foucaux) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 6 Jun 1887., (864i); ([4]p.)
  - Fowle, Charles W. A.L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 26 Jan 1912., (865); ([7]p.)
  - Fowle, Charles W. A.L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 12 Feb 1912., (866); ([3]p.)
  - Fowle, Charles W. A.L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 4 Jun 1913., (867); ([4]p.)
  - Fowle, Charles W. Typed L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Constantinople, 18 Jul 1913. 3l, (868)
  - Fowle, Charles W. Typed L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Constantinople, 11 Aug 1913., (869); 2l.
  - Fowle, Charles W. Typed L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Constantinople, 11 Oct 1913., (870); 1l.
  - Fowle, Charles W. A.L.s.(Charles W. Fowle) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Bethlehem, 2 Jan 1915., (871); ([4]p.)
    Enclosure: A. Memorandum s.(E. R. [i.e. Edith Howell (Perkins) Rockhill] [n.p., n.d.] [2]p.
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Winchester, 31 Dec [1902]., (872); ([4]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 8 Jun [1905]., (873); ([28]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 14 Jun [1905]., (874); ([15]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 17 Jun [1905]., (875); ([16]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 22 Jun [1905]., (876); ([12]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 21 Aug [1905]., (877); ([8]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 23 Aug [1905]., (878); ([4]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 30 Aug [1905], (879); ([4]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 11 Oct [1905]., (880); ([10]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chifoo, 21 May [1906]., (881); ([8]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Chefoo] 25 May [1906]., (882); ([7]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 6 Jul 1906., (883); [8]p.
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 20 Jul [1906]., (884); ([4]p.)
  - Fowler, John. Typed (c.c.)L.s. (John Fowler) to [James] L. Rodgers; Chefoo, 10 Jul 1906., (885); 1l.
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Chefoo] 11 Jul [1906]., (886); ([4]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 12 Oct 1906., (887); ([8]p.)
  - Fowler, John. A.L.s.(John Fowler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 9 Jul [1911]., (888); ([4]p.)
    Includes: "Corps D'Armée. Légion étrangère, 23 Oct. 1875.
  - Francis, Charles Spencer, 1853-1911. Typed L.s.(Charles S. Francis to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Troy, 10 Mar 1905., (889); 1l.
  - Francis, David Rowland, 1850-1927. A.L.s.(D. R. Francis) to "Mr. Secretary"; Washington, 9 Mar 1897., (890); 1l.
  - Francis, David Rowland, 1850-1927. Typed L.s.(David R. Francis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; St. Louis, 24 Nov 1906., (891); 1l.
  - Franow, A. A.L.s.(A. Franow) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] 20 Feb [1909], (892); ([1]p.)
  - Franow, A. A.L.s.(A. Franow) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] [1909], (893); ([3]p.)
  - Fraser, David. A.L.s.(David Fraser) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 12 Mar [1914]., (894); 2l.
  - Fraser, G. H. A.L.s.(G. H. Fraser) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Ichang, 21 Aug [1889]., (895); ([3]p.)
  - Fraser, G. H. A.L.s.(G. H. Fraser) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Ichang, 6 Nov [1889]., (896); ([8]p.)
  - Fraser, G. H. A.L.s.(G. H. Fraser) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Ichang, 4 Mar [1890]., (897); ([4]p.)
  - Frelinghuysen, Frederick Theodore, 1817-1885. Ms.L.s.(Fredk. T. Frelinghuysen) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 Apr 1884., (898); ([8]p.)
  - Frelinghuysen, Frederick Theodore, 1817-1885. Ms.L.s.(Fredk. T. Frelinghuysen) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 15 Jul 1884., (899); ([3]p.)
  - Freshfield, Douglas William, 1845-1935. A.L.s.(Douglas W. Freshfield) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [London] 31 Mar 1900., (900); ([3]p.)
  - Frothingham, Arthur Lincoln, 1859-1923. A.L.s.(A. L. Frothingham) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Princeton, 7 May [1895]., (901); 1l.
  - Gaiffiery, E. de. A.L.s.(E. de Gaiffiery) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Peking [n.d.], (902); ([4]p.)
  - Gallagher, H. J. Typed L.s.(H. J. Gallagher) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 8 Mar 1905., (903); ([1]p.)
  - Gallagher, Patrick, 1873- Typed L.s.(Patrick Gallagher) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 30 Jun 1914., (904); 2l.
  - Gallagher, Patrick, 1873- Typed (c.c.) of Article "China's Plenipotentiary of Peace"; [n.p., n.d.], (905); 4l.
  - Gannett, Henry, 1846-1914. Typed L.s.(Henry Gannett) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 15 Jul 1905., (906); 2l.
  - Garginlo, Ernestine. A.L.s.(Ernestine Garginlo) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Marseille, 18 Jul 1912. In French., (907); ([3]p.)
  - Garginlo, Ernestine. A.L.s.(Ernestine Garginlo) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Marseille, 1 Oct 1912., (908); ([2]p.)
  - Gaudemard, T. A.L.s.(T. Gaudemard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Le Havre, 31 Jan 1909., (909); ([3]p.)
  - Gaudemard, T. A.L.s.(T. Gaudemard) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Le Havre, 29 Aug 1909., (910); ([4]p.)
  - Gaudemard, T. A.L.s.(T. Gaudemard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; La Seyne, 2 Jan 1910., (911); ([3]p.)
  - Gauckler, Paul, 1866-1911. A.L.s.(P. Gauckler) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Tunis, 15 Feb 1898., (912); ([2]p.)
  - Gaullieur, Rosy. A.L.s.(Rosy Gaullieur) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Schnittweyerbad, 22 Jul [1913], (913); [2]p.
  - Gaullieur, Rosy. A.L.s.(Rosy Gaullieur) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Geneve, 8 Oct 1913., (914); ([4]p.)
  - Garnett, William James. A.L.s.(W. J. Garmett) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; St. Petersburg, (915); ([2]p.)
  - Garnett, William James. A.L.s.(W. J. Garnett) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lancaster, 8 Sep 1910., (916); ([4]p.)
  - Garnett, William James. A.L.s.(W. Garnett) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Tehran, 8 Apr 1914., (917); ([14]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; [n.p.] 16 Nov 1884., (918); ([1]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 1 Apr 1888., (919); ([2]p.)
  - Gart, Robert A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [ ] Rockhill; Peking, 28 Jul 1895., (919a); ([4]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 23 Apr 1900., (920); ([2]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 21 Dec 1904, (921); ([4]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 30 Apr 1905., (922); ([2]p.)
  - Gart, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Gart) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 26 Nov 1905., (923); ([2]p.)
  - Gates, Caleb Frank, 1857- Typed L.s.(C. F. Gates) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Constantinople 18 May 1911., (924); 1l.
  - Gaselee, Sir Alfred. A.L.s.(Alfred Gaselee) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 28 Aug 1902., (925); ([4]p.)
  - Gay, Jules. A.L.s.(Jules Gay) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Le Maus, 24 Mar 1898., (926); ([2]p.)
  - Gerhard, H. C. Typed L.s.(H. C. Gerhard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 30 Mar 1909., (927); 1l.
  - Gerhard, H. C. Typed L.s.(H. C. Gerhard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 31 Mar 1909., (928); 1l.
  - Gerhard, H. C. Typed L.s.(H. C. Gerhard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 16 Apr 1909., (929); 1l.
  - Gerhard, H. C. Typescript of Telegram to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 16 Apr 1909., (930); 1l.
  - Gibbons, James, card.,1834-1921. A.L.s.(James Card. Gibbons) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 2 Jun [1890]., (931); ([2]p.)
  - Gibbons, James, card., 1834-1921. A.L.s.(J. Card, Gibbons) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 12 Sep 1891., (932); ([2]p.)
  - Gilder, Joseph Benson, 1858-1936. A.L.s.(Joseph B. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 20 Jul 1900., (933); ([1]p.)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 8 Nov 1889., (934); 2l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 27 Nov 1889., (935); 2l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 5 Dec 1889., (936); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 9 Dec 1889., (937); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. A.L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 21 Feb 1890:, (938); ([2]p.)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. A.L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 7 Mar 1890., (939); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. A.L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 20 Jul 1900., (940); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Ms. Telegram s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 20 Jul 1900., (941); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 20 Jul 1900., (942); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 25 Jul 1900., (943); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 27 Jul 1900., (944); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 9 Aug 1900., (945); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 18 Sep 1890., (946); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. Typed L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William][Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 17 Apr 1903., (947); 1l.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1844-1909. A.L.s.(R. W. Gilder) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 14 May 1904., (948); 1l.
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. A.L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 6 May [189-?], (949); ([3]p.)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. A.L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 18 May [1891?], (950); ([1]p.)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. A.L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 30 Jun [1891]., (951); 1l.
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. A.L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 12 Apr [1897]., (952); ([4]p.)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. A. Article s.(Daniel C. Gilman); Baltimore, [190-?], (953); ([1]p.)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. Typed L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 24 Mar 1903., (954); 1l.
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. Typed L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 20 Apr 1903., (955); 1l.
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908. Typed L.s.(D. C. Gilman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 24 Apr 1903., (956); 1l.
  - Godoy, Jose Francisco, 1851- Typed L.s.(Jose F. Godoy) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Havana, 29 Jun 1909., (957); ([1]p.)
  - Goodnow, John. Typescipt of L.s.(John Goodnow, John F. Seaman) to Luh Hai Huan,; Cheng Hsuan-huai,; Wu ting fang; Shanghai, 23 Jun 1903., (958); 1l.
  - Goodnow, John. Typescript of L.s.(John Goodnow, etc.) to Luh Hai-huan,; Sheng Hsuan-Huai, and Wu Ting-fang; Shanghai, 3 Jul 1903., (959); 1l.
  - Goodnow, John. Typescript L.s.(John Goodnow) to Luh Hai Huan and Wu Ting-fang; [n.p.] 8 Jul 1903., (960); 1l.
  - Goodnow, John. Typescript of L.s.(John Goodnow, J. F. Seaman) to Luh Hai-huan,; Sheng Hsuan-huai, and Wu Ting-fang; Shanghai, 14 Jul 1903., (961); 1l.
  - Goodnow, John. Typescript of L.s.(John Goodnow, John F. Seaman) to Luh Hai-huan,; Sheng Hsuan-huai, and Wu Ting-fang; Shanghai, 17 Jul 1903., (962); 2l.
  - Goodnow, John. Typescript of No. 79 Treaty Commission s.(John Goodnow, J. F. Seaman) to John Hay, Shanghai, 17 Jul 1903., (963); 5l.
  - Goodnow, John. A.L.s.(John Goodnow) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 8 Apr 1904., (964); 1l.
  - Goode, George Brown, 1851-1896. Typed L.s.(G. Brown Goode) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 23 May 1891., (965); 2l.
  - Goode, George Brown, 1851-1896. Typed L.s.(G. Brown Goode) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Jun 1891., (966); 2l.
  - Goodrich, Joseph King. A.L.s.(Joseph K. Goodrich) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Kyoto, 2 Oct 1908., (967); ([4]p.)
  - Goodrich, Joseph King. A.L.s.(Joseph K. Goodrich) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Kyoto, 19 Nov 1908., (968); ([4]p.)
  - Goodrich, Joseph King. Typescript of L.s.(J. K. G.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 19 Nov 1908., (969); 1l.
  - Goodrich, Joseph King. A.L.s.(Joseph K. Goodrich) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Kyoto, 7 Feb 1909., (970); ([2]p.)
  - Goodrich, William Winton, 1833-1906. A.L.s.(W. W. Goodrich) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 11 Feb 1896., (971); ([1]p.)
  - Gordon-Cumming, Frances. A.L.s.(Frances Gordon-Cumming) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chester, 23 Jun [?], (972); ([4]p.)
  - Goschen, W. E A.L.s.(W.E.Goschen) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Pequot, 6 Oct 1894., (972a); ([4]p.)
  - Goschen, W E A.L.s.(W.E.Goschen) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 10 Oct [1894]., (972b); ([3]p.)
  - Goschen, W E A.L.s.(W.E.Goschen) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 11 Oct 1894., (972c); ([4]p.)
  - Giles, Lionel, 1875- A.L.s.(Lionel Giles) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 26 Oct 1913., (973); ([2]p.)
  - Gilsley, A. W. Typed L.s.(E. W.Gilsley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 28 Mar 1890., (974); ([1]p.)
  - Gipperich, G. Typescript of L.s.(G. Gipperich) to John Fowler; Chefoo, 5 Oct 1905., (975); 1l.
  - Goth, V. von A.L.s.(V. v Goth) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 16 Aug [1901], (976); ([4]p.)
  - Goth, V. von A.L.s.(V. v Goth) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 17 Aug 1901., (977); ([2]p.)
  - Gracey, Samuel Lewis. A.L.s.(Samuel L. Gracey) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Fuchau, 2 Jan [1906]., (978); 2l.
  - Graham, G. A. A.L.s.(G. A. Graham) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; St. Agathas Esplanade, 25 Feb [?], (979); ([4]p.)
  - Graham, G. A. A.L.s.(G. A. Graham) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; St. Agathas Esplanade, 2 Mar [?], (980); ([4]p.)
  - Grandprey, C. de. A.L.s.(C. de Grandprey) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Peking, 8 Jan 1901., (981); ([1]p.)
  - Grant, R. Suydam. A.L.s.(R. S. Grant) to "Dear General"[?]; New York, 15 May 1897., (982); 1l.
  - Grassi, Gregoire, bp. A.L.s.(Gregoire Grassi) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] [1890], (982a); (1l.)
  - Gray, G. W. A.L.s.(G. W. Gray) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 7 Jan [?], (983); ([1]p.)
  - Greely, A.W. A.L.s.(A.W.Greely) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 25 May 1893., (983a); (2l.)
  - Greene, Roger Sherman, 1840- A.L.s.(Roger S. Greene) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Vladivostok, 11 Mar 1907., (984); 7l.
  - Greene, Roger Sherman, 1840- Typed L.s.(Roger S. Greene) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Harbin, 15 Mar 1909., (985); 1l.